<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <name>VRE Sanguophage (HSK/CE Patched)</name>
    <packageId>vanillaracesexpanded.sanguophage</packageId>
    <author>Oskar Potocki, Sarg Bjornson, Erin — HSK/CE patch by CarbineAction</author>
    <modIconPath IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">UI/VELogo</modIconPath>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.5</li>
    </supportedVersions>
    <description>HSK/CE-patched standalone version of Vanilla Races Expanded — Sanguophage, tuned for the Hardcore SK modpack.

This bundles the upstream VRE Sanguophage mod content with HSK conventions and Combat Extended patches baked in. Do NOT enable the Steam Workshop version of VRE Sanguophage alongside this — they would duplicate each other's defs.

HSK conversion (6 deathrest / hemogen buildings rewritten to match HSK Biotech building patterns from Core_SK/Biotech/Patches/ThingDefs_Buildings/Buildings_Deathrest.xml):
- Switched from fixed Steel cost to stuffCategories Metallic + costStuffCount (HSK convention — build from any metal)
- Added the missing HSK class component pipeline (ElectronicComponents, Mechanism, Electronics, Microchips) so Sanguophage buildings cost similar to vanilla Biotech equivalents (Hemopump, HemogenAmplifier, DeathrestAccelerator, PsychofluidPump)
- Added Rubber, Plastic, CarbonAlloy minor materials as appropriate per building tier
- Kept HemogenPack as fuel cost (HSK Biotech convention)
- VRE_InvocationMatrix keeps GoldBar 40 for ritual flavor

CE patches:
- VRESanguophage_SharpTalons hediff — talons tool converted to CombatExtended.ToolCE with armor-penetration values (Sharp 0.65 / Blunt 2.0) that fit alongside the Saurid claws (Sharp 0.5) and other natural melee in this collection

Sanguophage abilities (HeartCrush, Hemosmosis, ToxicCloud, ViscousGoo, AcidSpray, etc.) are psycaster-style and do not need CE projectile conversion. The VRE_Proj_Goo projectile already has armorPenetrationBase/stoppingPower set and works under CE as-is. HemogenPack food items have no costList to convert.

Original mod by Oskar Potocki, Sarg Bjornson, Erin. HSK/CE conversion + bundling by CarbineAction.

Required: Hardcore SK, Combat Extended, Vanilla Expanded Framework, Biotech DLC. PsychofluidWell building only loads when Royalty DLC is active.</description>
    <modDependencies>
        <li>
            <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
            <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
            <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
        </li>
        <li>
            <packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
            <displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
            <downloadUrl>https://github.com/Vanilla-Expanded/VanillaExpandedFramework</downloadUrl>
        </li>
        <li>
            <packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</packageId>
            <displayName>RimWorld - Biotech</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1826140/RimWorld__Biotech/</steamWorkshopUrl>
        </li>
        <li>
            <packageId>skyarkhangel.HSK</packageId>
            <displayName>Hardcore SK</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2424766948</steamWorkshopUrl>
        </li>
        <li>
            <packageId>CETeam.CombatExtended</packageId>
            <displayName>Combat Extended</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2890901044</steamWorkshopUrl>
        </li>
    </modDependencies>
    <loadAfter>
        <li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
        <li>skyarkhangel.HSK</li>
        <li>CETeam.CombatExtended</li>
    </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>
