<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <name>VRE Hussar (HSK/CE Patched)</name>
    <packageId>CarbineAction.HSK.VRE.Hussar</packageId>
    <author>Oskar Potocki, xrushha, Taranchuk, Sarg Bjornson — HSK/CE patch by CarbineAction (CE patches adapted from Pacas Patches Compilation)</author>
    <modIconPath IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">UI/VELogo</modIconPath>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.5</li>
    </supportedVersions>
    <description>HSK/CE-patched standalone version of Vanilla Races Expanded — Hussar, tuned for the Hardcore SK modpack.

This bundles the upstream VRE Hussar mod content with HSK conventions and Combat Extended patches baked in. Do NOT enable the Steam Workshop version of VRE Hussar alongside this — they would duplicate each other's defs.

Bundled CE patches (adapted from Pacas Patches Compilation, then re-tuned for HSK CE armor scale):
- VREH_BulletproofSkin gene — natural kevlar-like armor rescaled to HSK CE values (Sharp 8 / Blunt 8, between flak and marine armor; Pacas's vanilla CE 5.0/5.0 was about half-flak under HSK CE math)
- VREH_BlackListedWeapons — extended with 56 entries so the WeaponAptitude gene system doesn't roll silly aptitudes like "aptitude in Mech Heavy Laser" or "aptitude in WoodLog":
  * Vanilla mech weapons (9, from Pacas) — Mech Blaster, Charge Lance, Inferno Cannon, etc.
  * Non-weapon items (6, from Pacas) — WoodLog, Bamboo, Kindling, etc.
  * Wolfein racial mech weapons (4, MayRequire-gated)
  * VFE Pirates warcasket-only guns (15, MayRequire-gated) — humanoids can't equip these
  * VFE Mechanoids mech weapons (22, MayRequire-gated)

Hussar is content-light (no recipes, no buildings, no costLists, no weapons, no apparel of its own — Hussars use vanilla weapons via the WeaponAptitude gene system). All HSK material conventions are preserved by default since there's nothing to convert.

Original mod by Oskar Potocki, xrushha, Taranchuk, Sarg Bjornson. CE patch baseline by Pacas. HSK/CE conversion + bundling by CarbineAction.

Required: Hardcore SK, Combat Extended, Vanilla Expanded Framework, Biotech DLC.</description>
    <modDependencies>
        <li>
            <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
            <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
            <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
        </li>
        <li>
            <packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
            <displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
            <downloadUrl>https://github.com/Vanilla-Expanded/VanillaExpandedFramework</downloadUrl>
        </li>
        <li>
            <packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</packageId>
            <displayName>RimWorld - Biotech</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1826140/RimWorld__Biotech/</steamWorkshopUrl>
        </li>
        <li>
            <packageId>skyarkhangel.HSK</packageId>
            <displayName>Hardcore SK</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2424766948</steamWorkshopUrl>
        </li>
        <li>
            <packageId>CETeam.CombatExtended</packageId>
            <displayName>Combat Extended</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2890901044</steamWorkshopUrl>
        </li>
    </modDependencies>
    <loadAfter>
        <li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
        <li>skyarkhangel.HSK</li>
        <li>CETeam.CombatExtended</li>
    </loadAfter>
    <incompatibleWith>
        <li>vanillaracesexpanded.hussar</li>
    </incompatibleWith>
</ModMetaData>
