<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	
	<XenotypeDef>
		<defName>VRE_Poluxkin</defName>
		<label>poluxkin</label>
		<description>Based on genetic data retrofitted from Gauranlen Inc.’s investment into dendrology following the Fall of Sorne, phytokins are plant-based humanoids with an emphasis on symmetry and symbiosis. Their ability to subsist only on sunlight and affinity with any and all plantlife make them especially suited to aiding newly established colonies or underperforming industrial farms.\n\nBased on research from the forest planet of Phytok that committed to extensive analysis on human-compatibility with psychic energy, phytokin xenogerms are typically exclusive to high-ranking, supporting roles in megacorporations and planetary governments. Their unique way of reproduction has resulted in many identical offspring, with each generation becoming successively more competent than their progenitor, further contributing to their extremely low numbers. Their affinity with plantlife, along with the side effect of extremely high and ever-increasing psychic sensitivity, mean that any phytokin xenohumans found on the Rim are always adapted to high-concept, dominant trees that are present on their residing planet.\n\nThis particular xenogerm has adapted itself to Polux trees, allowing it to germinate new Polux bushes and improve local Polux bushes’ ability to consume toxic waste. While they are also immune to toxicity, they have developed a psychological requirement to consume and metabolize toxic wastepacks regularly.</description>
		<descriptionShort>Powerful advisors to rulers and despots, poluxkins are beautiful and cunning and possess an ability to connect with a polux tree, greatly enhancing its abilities. They are immune to toxicity and in fact can help the environment by consuming and metabolizing waste. They are excellent at taking care of plants and reproduce via planting a saplingchild.</descriptionShort>
		<iconPath>UI/Icons/Xenotypes/Poluxkin</iconPath>
		<nameMaker>VRE_NamePhytokin</nameMaker>
		<chanceToUseNameMaker>1</chanceToUseNameMaker>
		<inheritable>true</inheritable>
		<genes>
			<li Name="AlphaGenesSwap">VRE_Female</li>
			<li>ToxicEnvironmentResistance_Total</li>
			<li>WoundHealing_Slow</li>
			<li>PsychicAbility_Extreme</li>
			<li>AptitudeRemarkable_Plants</li>
			<li>Hair_Grayless</li>
			<li>VRE_GreenThumb</li>
			<li>VRE_SaplingBirth</li>
			<li>VRE_Photosynthesis</li>
			<li>VRE_BarkSkin</li>
			<li>VRE_FoliageHair</li>
			<li>VRE_HairColor_Pollux</li>
			<li>VRE_SapBlood</li>
			<li>VRE_ProgressiveAttunement</li>
			<li>VRE_PoluxAffinity</li>
			<li>FireTerror</li>
			<li>MeleeDamage_Weak</li>
			<li>VerySleepy</li>
			<li>AptitudeTerrible_Melee</li>
			<li>AptitudeTerrible_Shooting</li>
			<li>AptitudeTerrible_Construction</li>
			
		</genes>
	</XenotypeDef>
</Defs>