<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <name>VRE Genie (HSK/CE Patched)</name>
    <packageId>CarbineAction.HSK.VRE.Genie</packageId>
    <author>Oskar Potocki, Sarg Bjornson — HSK/CE patch by CarbineAction (antibiotics redirect adapted from Pacas Patches Compilation)</author>
    <modIconPath IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">UI/VELogo</modIconPath>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.5</li>
    </supportedVersions>
    <description>HSK/CE-patched standalone version of Vanilla Races Expanded — Genie, tuned for the Hardcore SK modpack.

This bundles the upstream VRE Genie mod content with HSK conventions baked in. Do NOT enable the Steam Workshop version of VRE Genie alongside this — they would duplicate each other's defs.

HSK integration (adapted from Pacas Patches Compilation):
- Removes the standalone VRE_Antibiotics drug item, ChemicalDef, NeedDef, Tolerance, and Addiction hediffs — these don't fit HSK's medical economy where MedicalDrink already serves the antibiotic role
- Removes AddictionResistant_VRE_Antibiotics gene from the Genie xenotype (no longer needed since the drug is gone)
- Patches HSK's MedicalDrink (Items_Meals_Medical.xml from Core_SK) to grant the VRE_AntibioticsHigh hediff via VanillaRacesExpandedGenies.IngestionOutcomeDoer_GiveHediff_Discriminating, so Genies drinking medicinal alcohol still get their immunity boost
- Keeps the four high-tier antibiotics hediffs (VRE_AntibioticsHigh and the three weaker variants) so the discriminating outcome doer still has targets

Genie has no CE-relevant content (no recipes with raw materials, no buildings, no weapons, no apparel, no tools/verbs). All 16+ Genie genes are pure stat factors — Curiosity, Hemophiliac, BlueBlood, ElongatedHead, AptitudePhenomenal, Immunity, Slow_Diseases, WoundHealing — none need armor or CE patches.

Original mod by Oskar Potocki and Sarg Bjornson. HSK antibiotics redirect by Pacas. Bundling and HSK integration by CarbineAction.

Required: Hardcore SK, Combat Extended, Vanilla Expanded Framework, Biotech DLC.</description>
    <modDependencies>
        <li>
            <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
            <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
            <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
        </li>
        <li>
            <packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
            <displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
            <downloadUrl>https://github.com/Vanilla-Expanded/VanillaExpandedFramework</downloadUrl>
        </li>
        <li>
            <packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</packageId>
            <displayName>RimWorld - Biotech</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>https://store.steampowered.com/app/1826140/RimWorld__Biotech/</steamWorkshopUrl>
        </li>
        <li>
            <packageId>skyarkhangel.HSK</packageId>
            <displayName>Hardcore SK</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2424766948</steamWorkshopUrl>
        </li>
        <li>
            <packageId>CETeam.CombatExtended</packageId>
            <displayName>Combat Extended</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2890901044</steamWorkshopUrl>
        </li>
    </modDependencies>
    <loadAfter>
        <li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
        <li>skyarkhangel.HSK</li>
        <li>CETeam.CombatExtended</li>
    </loadAfter>
    <incompatibleWith>
        <li>vanillaracesexpanded.genie</li>
    </incompatibleWith>
</ModMetaData>
